<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<lang id="en">
	<langstring name="LNG_HELP">Show help</langstring>
	<langstring name="LNG_HELP_CLOSE">Close help window</langstring>
	<langstring name="LNG_HELP_NEXT">Next tip</langstring>
	<langstring name="LNG_HELP_PREV">Previous tip</langstring>
	
	<!-- Note: help messages should not contain new lines. Use <br/> tags instead. -->
	<langstring name="LNG_HELP1"><![CDATA[<b>Welcome</b><br/><br/>To navigate through this book either use the arrow keys on your keyboard (left, right) or click on the page's corners. You may also drag the pages by keeping the left mouse button pressed, then dragging away from a corner towards its opposite neighbor.<br/><br/>When closing this window, use the "?" button in the bar below the pages to open it again.]]></langstring>
	<langstring name="LNG_HELP1B"><![CDATA[<b>Welcome</b><br/><br/>To navigate through this book either use the arrow keys on your keyboard (left, right) or click on the page's corners. You may also drag the pages by keeping the left mouse button pressed, then dragging away from a corner towards its opposite neighbor.]]></langstring>
	<langstring name="LNG_HELP2"><![CDATA[<b>Navigation</b><br/><br/>Use the navigation below the pages to quickly jump from one page to another using the page buttons (the dots).<br/><br/>Thumbnails will be shown for the hovered page button. It might take a few seconds to generate the thumbnail for the first time, so please be patient.]]></langstring>
	<langstring name="LNG_HELP3"><![CDATA[<b>Zoom Mode</b><br/><br/>If there is a small magnifiying glass on a page (usually on top of an image) this means there is higher resolution version available. Click on the magnifying glass to open zoom mode.<br/><br/>In zoom mode, use the mousewheel to zoom in and out. If the image is larger than the display area, drag the image or the rectangle on the thumbnail (top right) to move the visible area.<br/><br/>If the image is part of a gallery two arrow buttons will appear in the box in the top right corner, which may be used to navigate between images in that gallery.<br/><br/>Use the X button in the thumbnail box or the ESC key to exit the zoom mode.]]></langstring>
	<langstring name="LNG_HELP4"><![CDATA[<b>Fullscreen</b><br/><br/>Use the leftmost button in the navigation bar to enable fullscreen mode. Its main purpose is to allow a better display of zoomed images, as in fullscreen mode the whole screen is used for zoom mode, in contrast to just the area two pages take in non-fullscreen.<br/><br/>Usually entering zoom mode also triggers a change to fullscreen mode. If this is not the case you may use that button to enter fullscreen mode manually.]]></langstring>
	<langstring name="LNG_HELP5"><![CDATA[<b>Slideshow</b><br/><br/>The button in the navigation with the "play" symbol will toggle the slideshow mode, i.e. automatic page turning. Every page will then be displayed for a certain amount of time before an automatic page turn to the next page is triggered.]]></langstring>
</lang>